bside.com 2012-08-28

# B-Side – The audience is never wrong » Privacy Policy

## Introduction

B-Side Entertainment, Inc. ("B-Side") has created this Privacy Policy in order to disclose its use of consumer data collected about you. This Privacy Policy is effective as of September 1, 2005. Any questions regarding this policy should be directed by email to privacy@bside.com. You may also contact B-Side at 815 Brazos Street Suite 300, Austin, TX 78701. The following discloses B-Side’s information gathering and dissemination practices for its marketing website.

## Information Collected and Received

B-Side may collect or receive information about each person who registers with the B-Side website including, but not limited to, user name, password, first and last name, email address, street address, gender, occupation, and interests. B-Side also collects information on the pages you access and other information you may volunteer, such as survey information.

## Uses of Information

WE WILL NEVER SELL YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS, OR ANY OTHER PERSONAL INFORMATION, TO ANY THIRD PARTY. EVER.

Except as described in this section, we will not disclose your personal information to any third party without notifying you of our intent to share the information and giving you an opportunity to prevent your information from being shared.

From time to time, we may partner with companies based on the interests of our users. These partner companies will never see your email address or any other information that could identify you or be used to contact you directly.

Any exceptions to this policy of sharing your name, address or email address with a partner company will be done only with your permission.

B-side reserves the right to disclose information when required by law.

We occasionally use other companies to perform services necessary to our operations. In the course of providing these services, those companies may have access to your personal information. By contractual agreement, those companies must treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, we will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies.

B-Side may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with B-Side’s server and to administer B-Side’s web site. Your IP address may also be used to help identify you and your online profile and to gather broad demographic information.

B-Side’s site’s registration form requires users to give B-Side contact information (such as your name and email address) and demographic information (such as your zip code, age, or income level). B-Side uses customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about B-Side and promotional material from some of B-Side’s partners. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the user when necessary. B-Side may use demographic and/or profile data to tailor the visitor’s experience on B-Side’s site, show the visitor content that B-Side thinks you may be interested in, and display content according to your preferences. The demographic and profile data will be shared with advertisers ONLY on an aggregate basis.

We may also disclose, on an anonymous basis, statements made by our customers.

## Email Communication

## Security

B-Side uses industry-standard technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged between B-Side and other companies to help ensure its security. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under B-Side’s control. B-Side’s servers are backed up regularly and protected by security systems.

## Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. B-Side’s site uses cookies to keep track of your session, shopping cart, and advertising delivery. B-Side may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password. B-Side may use an outside ad company to display ads on B-Side’s site. These ads may also contain cookies. While B-Side uses cookies in other parts of B-Side’s web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by B-Side’s ad company and B-Side does not have access to this information.

## Links

B-Side may create links to other web sites. B-Side will make a reasonable effort to link only to sites that meet similar standards for maintaining each individual’s right to privacy. However, many other sites that are not associated or authorized by B-Side may have links leading to B-Side’s site. B-Side cannot control these links and B-Side is not responsible for any content appearing on these sites.

## Ammendments

B-Side may amend this policy at any time. If B-Side is going to use personally identifiable information collected through B-Side’s corporate site in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection B-Side will notify users via email and/or by posting a notice on B-Side’s Web site for 30 days prior to such use. This Agreement may not be otherwise amended except in a writing that specifically refers to this Privacy Policy and is physically signed by both parties.

## Contacts

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact privacy@bside.com. Upon request, B-Side will provide you with access to information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that B-Side collects and maintains about you. This site gives you the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: (i) email: privacy@bside.com; or (ii) visit www.bside.com. There you can also log into your account to update your contact information.

## Communication & Opt-Out

B-Side occasionally emails registered users with information on new releases on bside.com or updates on B-Side festival sites the user has visited. Additionally, B-Side users can select to receive or disable more specific notifications by logging in and editing their user profiles at <http://www.bside.com/your/edit>.

B-Side provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from B-Side. To opt-out of receiving our communications, you can (i) submit your email address in the following form; (ii) send email to remove@bside.com; or (iii) send postal mail to: 815 Brazos Street Suite 300, Austin, TX 78701.
